doctors they go beyond the call of duty
and in today's time they are our only
lifeline
in doctors we see a reflection of the
divine
that's why we believe that for a doctor
like you
just a thank you won't do icici bank
salutes lifesavers like you for your
selfless service
introducing icici bank salute doctors
banking solutions
because we understand your hectic life
and that
every moment of yours is precious so we
bring to you a one-stop banking offering
with instant and easy solutions that
save time
and let you focus on healing lives
whether you are a medical student a
sanitary consulting doctor
a clinic or hospital owner we have the
right solutions for you
like a dedicated relationship manager to
cater to your banking needs
a range of solutions to aid your
professional growth
with everything from term of business
loans
medical equipment funding to working
capital management
solutions to manage your day-to-day
operations
like payment collection services
connected banking
tax payments insurance exclusive
offers and discounts for your
professional needs
ranging from dedicated concierge
services
for clinic setup online consultation
setup to subscriptions of healthcare
journals
and more we also have a whole range of
easy and time-saving solutions
to manage your personal banking needs
like wealth management family banking
real estate advisory loans
credit cards health and protection plans
forex solutions exclusive lifestyle
offers and luxury concierge services
icici banks salute doctors banking
solutions
puts together a wide array of instant
and easy offerings for busy doctors
like you after all your time is
literally worth
lives and this is our way to salute
you and honor you for your undying
spirit